{
    "id": "7599bd2a97ef426eaf93a9c45cf533dd",
    "title": "Nouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The winners were two …………………………. from the north.",
            "description": "Woman is the right word. Female is usually an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "women",
                "womans",
                "females"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He took …………………………….. at this.",
            "description": "These are idiomatic expressions. ",
            "answers": [
                "insult",
                "offence"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His brother is a …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drunker",
                "drunkard"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There are many ……………………………. in the developing countries.",
            "description": "Poor is an adjective. It is used with a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "poors",
                "poor people"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The clock has struck ……………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nine",
                "nine hours"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher taught us a new ……………………………….",
            "description": "Poetry is essentially a collection of poems.",
            "answers": [
                "poem",
                "poetry"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no ……………………………… on the bus.",
            "description": "This is an idiomatic expression. ",
            "answers": [
                "space",
                "place",
                "room"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He provided ……………………………….. with food.",
            "description": "The poor means all poor people. ",
            "answers": [
                "poors",
                "poor people",
                "the poor"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have packed my ………………………………",
            "description": "Luggage does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "luggage",
                "luggages"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "One of my ……………………………. has left.",
            "description": "Use a plural noun after one of.",
            "answers": [
                "servants",
                "servant"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The rich man didn’t give the beggar ……………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anything",
                "nothing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It is very cold in this …………………………….. of the country.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "side",
                "part"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}